intheircloset.com 2018-12-03

# Privacy Policy

This statement covers the website **[http://intheircloset.com](http://intheircloset.com/)** (InTheirCloset.com). Please read this statement carefully before accessing InTheirCloset.com. Your use of InTheirCloset.com indicates your agreement to abide by the terms in effect.

  * Information Collection
  * Comments
  * Cookies
  * Third Party Cookies
  * Third Party Advertising
  * Log Files
  * Legal Disclaimer
  * Business Transitions
  * Links
  * Notification of Changes
  * Contact Information

### Information Collection

The owner of InTheirCloset.com is the sole owner of the information collected on InTheirCloset.com. InTheirCloset.com may collect information from its users at several different points on its website. No information collected will ever be sold, transferred, or given away by InTheirCloset.com unless this sentence is deleted, if so then you are on your own.

### Comments

In order to enhance their use of this website, users can choose to leave comments on particular articles of interest. To leave a comment, users must submit information including a valid email address. InTheirCloset.com uses this information to screen out users who leave comments prohibited by our terms and conditions of use, and will not pass this information to any other organization.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small information file that is sent to your computer, mobile or other device when you visit a website and it will recognise your device on future visits. These types of files do a number of different jobs such as remembering your preferences and chosen items, assisting you to improve your site experience as well as trying to ensure that the adverts or offers you see online are more relevant to you. These “cookies” can be divided into 4 types each of which is outlined below.

Category 1: Strictly Necessary Cookies

These cookies are essential in order to enable the site to provide services you have asked for.

Category 2: Performance Cookies

This type collect anonymous information on how people use the site and the data is merged with other users to enable us to improve how the site operates. For example we utilise Google Analytics cookies to help us understand how customers arrive at our site, browse or use our site and highlight areas where we can improve areas such as navigation, shopping experience and marketing campaigns. The data stored by these cookies never shows personal details from which your individual identity can be established.

Category 3: Functionality Cookies

These remember choices you make such as language, search parameters such as size, colour or product line. These can then be used to provide you with an experience more appropriate with your selections and make the visits more tailored and pleasant. The information is also merged with other users on an anonymous basis to enable us to improve how the site operates.

Category 4: Targeting Cookies or Advertising Cookies

These cookies collect information about your browsing habits in order to make advertising relevant to you and your interests. They remember the websites you have visited and that information is shared with other parties such as advertisers.

You can change the settings on your browser to prevent cookies from being stored on your computer or mobile device without your explicit consent. Your browser help section will normally provide details on how to manage the cookie settings. Otherwise, read [here](http://www.aboutcookies.org/DEFAULT.ASPX?page=2) on how to delete cookies on your browser.

### Third Party Cookies

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, InTheirCloset.com has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by InTheirCloset.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Third Party Advertising

The advertisements appearing on InTheirCloset.com are delivered to users by Google, among other services. Information about users’ visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not username, date of birth, or any other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site. No personal information about our users is ever transferred to any party by InTheirCloset.com.

### Log Files

Like most standard website servers we make use of log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the website, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

### Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, InTheirCloset.com may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our website.

### Business Transitions

In the event InTheirCloset.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

### Links

InTheirCloset.com contains links to other websites. Please be aware that InTheirCloset.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our website to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by InTheirCloset.com.

### Notification of Changes

Whenever InTheirCloset.com changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

### Contact Information

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please do not hesitate to contact us at [mail@intheircloset.com ****](mailto:mail@intheircloset.com).
